Stoinks
Labrinth
Do you think I am stupid?
Do you think I am bat shit crazy‚
having you on my mind?
Do you think I am helpless?
My algebra gon′ equal you every time
Do you think I am calling?
Do you think I am calling out
your name every night?
Girl‚ I have fallen for you
What‚ what you say?
Oh‚ my God
Baby‚ baby‚ don′t you see
I got everything you need
Only a genius could love
a woman like she
Oh‚ my God
Baby‚ baby‚ don′t you see
I got everything you need
Only a genius could love
a woman like she
I am a genius
A genius
He is a genius
Cause I love a woman like you
I am a genius
A genius
He is a genius
′Cause I love a woman like you
Sia
You′ll be my Einstein‚ my Newton‚
my Galileo‚ and my Hawking
Boy‚ put that pep in my step
Put your arm on my neck
while I am walking
Please understand‚ yeah I have
fallen for you‚ you
What‚ what you say?
Oh‚ my God
Baby‚ baby don′t you see
I got everything you need
Only a genius could love
a woman like me
Sayin′ oh‚ my God
Baby‚ baby don′t you see
I got everything you need
Only a genius could love
a woman like me
I am a genius
A genius
He is a genius
′Cause I love a woman like you
I am a genius
A genius
He is a genius
Cause I love a woman like you
Oh‚ my God
Dot the I′s and cross the T′es
I got everything you need
Well‚ only a genius could
love a woman like me
Oh‚ my God
You are the lock and I am the key
I got everything you need
Well‚ only a genius could
love a woman like me
′Cause I love a woman like you
He he He is a genius
Cause I love a woman like you
Stoinks